uniden.com 2018-10-18

# Privacy Policy - Uniden

This Privacy Policy applies only to web sites maintained by Uniden America Corporation (“Uniden”) and to information provided by you or otherwise collected online through a Uniden web site.

###### Information Collected and Its Use

In general, you can visit this web site without telling us who you are or giving us personally identifiable information about yourself. There are portions of this web site where you may provide us with personally identifiable information, so as, for example, to provide you with information you request, to purchase products on our Online Store, and for Product Registration of your purchased new Uniden products. Such personally identifiable information may include your name, address, telephone number, email address, and other identifiers that may assist us in contacting you. We may use the personally identifiable information you provide to contact you about new products, services, promotions and other information that we believe may be of interest to you. We may use mailings, e-mail and telephone calls to contact you. We may also share the information you provide with Uniden affiliates and other companies.

For those customers who purchase products online from us, credit card information will be collected. This information is collected in order to process your purchases and will be shared with others only to the extent needed to fulfill or to collect payment for your purchase.

###### California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights

If you reside in California, you may have the right to receive from Uniden the names of all companies, if any, with whom we have shared personal information pertaining to you and your family within the past year for direct marketing purposes. This may be so, whether such information has been obtained by way of this web site or otherwise. To request the names of such companies and the categories of personal information disclosed, you must make your written request by United States Mail, postage prepaid, addressed to: Uniden Privacy, Uniden America Corporation, 3001 Gateway Drive, Suite 130, Irving, TX 75063. Be sure to provide in the request sufficient information to properly identify you and/or the members of your family. The information you provide in your request will be used only to identify the companies, if any, with whom we have shared your personal information. Uniden can respond to such requests only if made by United States Mail to this address and not otherwise. Uniden will respond to your request by United States Mail.

###### Remarketing

Uniden uses remarketing techniques involving cookies to show you related ads on other third-party websites that you may visit. Cookies are small pieces of data stored in your web browser that contain information about your visit to our website. Third-party vendors (including Google) will use these cookies to serve ads based on your past visits to our website. You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google Ads Preferences Manager (https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/) or you can also visit the Network Advertising Initiative (http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) opt-out page to opt-out of a third party vendor’s use of these cookies.

###### Changes to this Privacy Policy

You may inform yourself of any changes in this privacy policy by periodically checking it online. Uniden reserves the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy at any time and from time to time without advance notice.

###### Effective Date

This privacy policy was last changed on October 30, 2012.
